

 $\times$ 

mailtojustinj@gmail.com

+1 (214) 836 3006

Q

4418 Warbler LN, Garland, Texas, 75043, United States America

05 August, 1993

justinjj16.github.io/justinjosep h/home

in

linkedin.com/in/justinjj16

**(7)** 

github.com/justinjj16

1/2

stackoverflow.com/story/justinjj08

(O)

instagram.com/justinjj16

### **SKILLS**

JavaScript

React

AWS

React-Native

Mode

Graphql

Fynress

redux-saga

Postgress

Angular

### **LANGUAGES**

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Malayalam

Full Professional Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Fitness

Golf

# Justin Joseph

Software Engineer

Experienced Software Engineer with demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in JavaScript, React, Angular, node js, Redux-saga, cloud functions. Strong engineering professional with a Master (MSc) focused in Computer Science from Mahatma Gandhi University

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

React, Angular, React-Native, JavaScript, TypeSript, Node, Express, Graphql, AWS

Neoito

09/2019 - Present Thiruvananthapuram

**JavaScript** 

Adhoc Technologies

07/2018 - 09/2019 Thiruvananthapuram

### **EDUCATION**

## **MSc Computer Science**

College of Applied Science, Payyappady

09/2014 - 12/2017 61%

**BSc Computer Science** 

NMCC. Marthanam

07/2011 - 04/2014 64%

**Higher Secondary** 

Concordia Lutheran Higher Secondary School

06/2009 - 05/2011 63%

**Secondary School** 

Government Model Boys Higher Secondary School

06/2009 70%